Guide to the de Caro, Mulvehill and Menkhoff Family Papers 1880-2001 MS 2956
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
- Series III: Photographs, 1880-1970
  - Subseries III.4: de Caro Family Photographs
    - Frank A. de Caro, Ann Menkhoff de Caro, and Frank E. de Caro at their family home, circa 1940-1949 (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - Frank A. de Caro (according to information written by his daughter, he is wearing stickpins presented to him by the Italian monarchs), undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Frank A. de Caro with son Frank E. de Caro, circa 1943 (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - Frank A. de Caro with Frank E. de Caro (in army uniform) and Frank de Caro, circa 1944 (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - Frank A. de Caro with son-in-law John Santo in front of his residence at 725 Greenwood Ave in Brooklyn, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - Frank A. de Caro with grandson, circa 1950-1959 (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Frank A. de Caro with daughter Elsa de Caro Napolis in Monroe, NY where she and her husband developed property, circa 1960-1969 (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - Frank A. de Caro on porch of office for housing development in Monroe, NY, undated (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Frank A. de Caro, undated (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - Frank A. de Caro, 1886-1955 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Frank E. de Caro, circa 1920-1929 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - Frank E. de Caro in the streets of New York City, circa 1930-1939 (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - Frank E. de Caro, photograph taken from a cigarette ad (he worked as a model during the Depression), circa 1930-1939 (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - Frank E. de Caro in uniform with wife Beatrice Mulvehill, father Frank A. de Caro, and son Frank de Caro (photo booklet), circa 1944 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - Frank E. de Caro in uniform in front of family home, circa 1940-1949 (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Frank E. de Caro and Beatrice Mulvehill de Caro clamming, undated (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - Frank de Caro held by his mother Beatrice Mulvehill de Caro with Frank E. de Caro, circa 1943 (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - Frank de Caro held by Anna Menkhoff de Caro with Beatrice Mulvehill de Caro, Frances de Caro, Lillyan de Caro Santo, and Frank A. de Caro., circa 1943 (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - Frank de Caro, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - Frank de Caro college portrait, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - Frank de Caro with either his father Frank E. de Caro or his grandfather Frank A. de Caro, undated (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - William de Caro, son of Frank A de Caro and Anna Menkhoff de Caro who died of spinal meningitis as a child, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Jennifer McAlevey and Arthur DiRocco wedding picture, undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - John McAlevey and grandson Giffin DiRocco, undated (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - August Menkhoff, circa 1890-1910 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Maria Meyer Menkhoff, circa 1890-1910 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Maria Meyer Menkhoff and August Menkhoff (Parents of Anna Menkhoff de Caro), undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Bertha Meyer (1848-1903), aunt of Anna Menkhoff de Caro, circa 1880-1900 (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - Ed Napolis, undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Ed Napolis (husband of Elsa de Caro), 1961 (Box 3, Folder 128)
    - Ed Napolis and Elsa de Caro Napolis with a number of transportation innovations in which the couple invested, circa 1920-1929 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Elsa de Caro Napolis and Ed Napolis, undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Elsa de Caro Napolis, undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Lillyan de Caro (Santo), undated (Box 4, Folder 37-38)
    - Lillyan de Caro Santo, undated (Box 3, Folder 129)
    - Lillyan de Caro Santo and John Santo, undated (Box 3, Folder 130)
    - Lillyan de Caro Santo (in several group photographs), undated (Box 3, Folder 131)
    - Lillyan de Caro [Santo] on maiden voyage of S.S. America, from New York, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 132)
    - Lillyan and John Santo in a cocktail lounge in Windham, NY, 1948 August 28 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Lillyan de Caro Santo and John Santo at the Casablanca Gardens night club in Brooklyn, undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Lillyan de Caro Santo, circa 2000 (Box 3, Folder 133)
    - Children of Frank A. de Caro and Anne Menkhoff de Caro, Elsa, Francis, Arthur, Gertrude, and Lillyan, circa 1900-1920 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Group portrait of Frank E. de Caro, Anna Menkhoff de Caro, Arthur de Caro and Frank A. de Caro sailing to Italy, 1921 (Box 3, Folder 134)
    - Unidentified, Frank de Caro, and Frances de Caro at Saint Marks in Venice, 1921 (Box 3, Folder 135)
    - Unidentified, Frances de Caro, and Arthur de Caro, circa 1920-1929 (Box 3, Folder 136)
    - Lillyan de Caro Santo and Frank E. de Caro, circa 1943 (Box 3, Folder 137)
    - Lillyan de Caro, Frank de Caro, Beatrice Mulvehill, and Frank E. de Caro, circa 1943 (Box 3, Folder 138)
    - Frances de Caro, Lillyan de Caro Santo, Frank A. de Caro, Beatrice Mulvehill de Caro, Anna Menkhoff and Frank de Caro, circa 1944 (Box 3, Folder 139)
    - Wedding of Lillyan de Caro and John Santo, New York, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Christmas 1947 (Box 3, Folder 140)
    - Frances de Caro, Lillyan de Caro Santo, and unidentified friend, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 141)
    - Frances de Caro, Lillyan de Caro Santo, Anna Menkhoff de Caro and John Santo, circa 1950-1959 (Box 3, Folder 142)
    - Sales office of Monroe, NY, circa 1950-1959 (Box 3, Folder 143)
    - de Caro family at dining table at their family home, circa 1950-1959 (Box 3, Folder 144)
    - de Caro family gatherings, circa 1950-1959 (Box 3, Folder 145)
    - de Caro family Thanksgiving, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 146)
    - Ed Napolis, Frances de Caro, Anna Menkhoff de Caro, Elsa de Caro Napolis, Frank de Caro, in Monroe, NY, circa 1960-1969 (Box 3, Folder 147)
    - Wedding of Ricky Beattie and his bride Margot, 1985 August 17 (Box 3, Folder 148)
    - Frank A. de Caro, Elsa de Caro Napolis, and Ed Napolis, undated (Box 3, Folder 149)
    - de Caro and D'Angelo business on Grand Street in New York City, undated (Box 3, Folder 150)
    - Cottage at Lake Waramaug, CT where the de Caro family spent summers, undated (Box 3, Folder 151)
    - New Hampshire house of John McAlevey, undated (Box 3, Folder 152)
    - Interlaken Inn, where Frank and Anna de Caro spent summers, undated (Box 3, Folder 153)
    - de Caro residence at 725 Greenwich Avenue in Brooklyn, undated (Box 4, Folder 43-44)